My name is Kristy I'm working at the Curves in West Jordan Utah.
We are talking about weight loss tips.
A really good way to lose weight sometimes is a support group.
Having friends to do it with you, family members or even joining the support group.
At curves we do offer nutrition classes, that is a group of ladies that are all the same goal, we meet once a week and we talk about suggestions for each other.
Tips on different salad dressings we've used that are lower fat that taste better.
Just to have a group of women doing it with you or even friends, or a spouse, someone that's there to support you that knows what you are going through.
And can help you through it and you can help them.
So you know if you want to find one you can bring a friend if not if you do go to a facility like curves or other facilities they do offer support groups where you can do it with a group of friends and you can all lose weight together.
Another part of our support group is we , with these ladies on the wall, they make a paper doll that resembles themselves and if they come to curves at least three times a week through the busy summer where a lot of people make it, find it hard to work out, they stay in our camp and we keep track of them call them let them know that we are, they haven't hit there three times a week that week.
And there's different ways to we support our ladies through exercising three times a week.